<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<document xmlns="http://maven.apache.org/XDOC/2.0"
          xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:schemaLocation="http://maven.apache.org/XDOC/2.0 http://maven.apache.org/xsd/xdoc-2.0.xsd">
    <properties>
        <title>JJSON - A JSON Library for Java without dependencies</title>
        <author email="grobmeier@gmail.com">Christian Grobmeier</author>
    </properties>
  <!-- Optional HEAD element, which is copied as is into the XHTML <head> element -->
    <head>
        <style type="text/css">
            h2 {
            font-size: 50px;
            }
        </style>
    </head>
    <body>
    <!-- The body of the document contains a number of sections -->
        <section name="JJSON - A JSON Library for Java without dependencies">
            <p>JJSon is a simple API for dealing with the JSON format. It needs no dependencies and just offers the 
                features you really need to work. You can find the JSON Specification there: http://www.json.org
            </p>
  
            <p>JJSON actually uses some code from Apache Commons Lang. The code is shaded into the jar file,
            and so you don't need to care about this. The Lang-Classes were relocated to the jjson-Package,
            you are save to use your own version of Commons Lang. In addition, only a part of this jar is delivered.</p> 
  
            <p>There is a Struts 2 plugin available, which can be used as a result type to return JSON Strings.
            </p>
        </section>

        <section name="Features">
            <ul>
                <li>Using annotations to create json strings out of objects</li>
                <li>Map json strings into POJOs</li>
                <li>Creating a java object net out of a json string</li>
                <li>Creating a json string out of a java object net</li>
            </ul>
        </section>

        <section name="Why another JSon-Lib for Java?">
            I just didn't want to have complex implementations of this simple notation- most of the features other libs gave to me i didn't use. If you feel the same you should consider to contact me (on the dev list) and contribute some patches. You are welcome.
        </section>

        <section name="State of development">
            <p>The new version should work for a lots of cases. Mapping with annotations and working with json using the apis objects work in both directions.</p>
            <p>The struts 2 plugin is pretty new and has the ususal flaws.</p>
        </section>

        <section name="Backwards cmpatibility">
            <p>
                Release numbers will have the follow format: <b>major.minor.patch</b>
                
                <ul>
                    <li>Breaking backwards compatibility bumps the major</li>
                    <li>Backward compatible changes bumps the minor</li>
                    <li>Backward compatible Bug fixes bump the patch</li>
                </ul>
                
                Please also see: http://semver.org/
            </p>
        </section>
        
        <section name="License">
            <p>Copyright 2007 - 2012 Christian Grobmeier</p>
            <p>Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0: http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0</p>
        </section>
        
    </body>
</document>